Guide to the Washington State University Audio/Video Materials 1930-2005
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
Washington State University Audio/Video Materials
1930-2005
Washington State University Libraries, Manuscripts, Archives and Special Collections
Archives 349
Washington State University.
18.5 Linear feet of shelf space 23 boxes
The collection comprises audio and video produced by, for, or about Washington State University, dating from 1930 up to 2005. However, the majority of the media is from the 1980s, 1990s, and 2000s. Included in the collection are news stories, promotional videos, recordings of significant performances, events, and speakers, and unfinished stock footage used in creating these and other productions.
The majority of the collection is video recordings, primarily VHS tapes and U-matic 3/4" tapes. Other videotape formats include S-VHS, M II, Betacam, BetacamSP, and one open reel 1" Type C. Other non-tape video include digital media on DVD, CD, and MiniDV; and film in 16mm and Super 16mm. Audio formats include 1/8" standard audio cassette tapes, 1/4" open reel tapes (reel-to-reel), and one 8-track tape.
Be aware that MASC may lack on-premises equipment for reproducing or even playing some formats.
Washington State University as an institution dates to 1890, when it was authorized by the newly-formed State of Washington. WSU's history is documented in numerous pieces of film and video, the oldest known being film footage of the Jan. 1 1916 "Rose Bowl" football game played in Pasadena, California.
The collection comprises audio and video produced by, for, or about Washington State University, dating from 1930 up to 2005. However, the majority of the media is from the 1980s, 1990s, and 2000s. Included in the collection are news stories, promotional videos, recordings of significant performances, events, and speakers, and unfinished stock footage used in creating these and other productions. Video found here was created by numerous sources, notably WSU's various news services and its campus television and radio stations. Many of the items were created by non-WSU organizations, either in the form of news (or other) stories about the school, or in the form of promotional or other materials contracted to other institutions by campus departments.
It is important to be aware that much of the description of this collection comes from the labels on the media or the containers they came in; it was not possible to view all the materials to determine accuracy of the labeling. As a result, users may discover upon viewing these items that their contents do not match their labels, and a few items have been discarded since this collection was created after we discovered the actual contents were not related to Washington State University. In some cases duplicate copies of materials are retained; this is primarily due to the significance of the material in question and the ongoing deterioration of electronic media, as well as due to the fact that uncertain labeling means items may not match their description, and that similarly (but not identically) named items may not actually be the same thing.
The majority of the collection is video recordings, primarily VHS tapes and U-matic 3/4" tapes. Other videotape formats include S-VHS, M II, Betacam, BetacamSP, and one open reel 1" Type C. Other non-tape video include digital media on DVD, CD, and MiniDV; and film in 16mm and Super 16mm. Audio formats include 1/8" standard audio cassette tapes, 1/4" open reel tapes (reel-to-reel), and one 8-track tape.
Be aware that MASC may lack on-premises equipment for reproducing or even playing some formats in this collection.
The collection is arranged in seven primary series, plus two significant subseries. Due to the disparate sizes of the different forms of media, organization within each series is frequently by media type. Within each media type, organization is primarily chronological, with undated materials ordered alphabetically at the end.
The description of each item includes what information we have on it, followed by the format of the item, followed by length of the recording (or the tape) if known.
The seven series are:
Series 1, Speakers and Presentations: Audio/video of presentations which occurred at or are associated with Washington State University.
Series 2, Recruitment and Promotional Material: Audio/video created for the express purpose or recruiting students and/or faculty to come to WSU, or to promote WSU to students, alumni, or the world in general. Though not labeled as its own subseries, the final box in this series contains the longer and more significant films.
Series 3, Campus Stock Footage / B-Roll: This is primarily non-completed material; original footage taken for use in creating other works. There are two subseries within this series. Subseries 3.1 contains materials collected by Andrews Greenspan and Associates in 1994, and Subseries 3.2 contains what appears to be footage of archival materials, probably filmed in WSU's Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections or similar facilities.
Series 4, Libraries: Footage from the construction of the Holland and Terrell Libraries, or presentations and materials related to the Libraries.
Series 5, Performing Arts and Fine Arts: Musical or artistic performances and shows preformed at/by or relating to Washington State University.
Series 6, WSU-Produced News Stores and Other Materials: Audio/Video news stories produced and aired by the various WSU media outlets, as well as other materials produced by campus organizations.
Series 7, News Footage and Produced Programs from Non-Campus Sources: News stories produced and aired by regional news media not affiliated with WSU, but relating to the school. Also included are a small number of non-news productions which are assumed to have WSU ties.
As noted above, description (and thus organization) was based upon labels, not upon viewing. As dates or further information about items is uncovered that will be edited into the description below, which may result in oddities, such as dated items appearing in the sequences of undated materials.
This collection is open and available for research use.
The materials in this collection came from a number of disparate accessions which had been transferred to Washington State University Libraries' Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections (MASC) over a period of years. Collections which were part of the original organizing process include: UA1985-54, UA1989-18, UA1995-01, UA2001-10, UA2002-05, UA2003-02, UA 2004-12, UA2005-09, UA2005-15, UA2006-07, UA2006-11, UA2006-13, UA2007-02, UA2008-15, and UPC-0007. The majority of those collections come from WSU News Services, the Office of the President, University Relations, the Instructional Media Center, and WSU Events.
Several other MASC collections were processed (at least partially) out of the same accessions as these materials. These include:
Archives 320. "WSU Presents" Recordings, 1992-2004.
Archives 325. “The Great Russian” Production Films, 1960.
Archives 328. Office of the President Audio and Video Recordings, 1937-2006.
SC 013. Eastern Washington Historical Media Collection, 1928-1987.
Further WSU-specific audio/video is held in numerous collections within MASC as well as in the WSU Libraries proper.
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Washington State University -- History.; State College of Washington -- History.; Washington State University -- Archives.; State College of Washington -- Archives.
Universities and colleges -- Washington (State) -- Pullman.
Colleges and Universities; Washington (State); Moving Images; Sound Recordings
- SERIES 1: SPEAKERS AND PRESENTATIONS.
  - Distinguished Faculty Address. "Paradoxes of Marketing Success" Edna Douglas. Instructional Television Service. Inside case is paper News Service 2-p release. Tape Number PROV 1. Video: 3/4" U-matic. 57:53, 1980 March 12 (Box 1, Item 1)
  - WSU Faculty Address. Bryan and Dr. Douglas. Video: 3/4" U-matic. 60 min., 1980 March 12 (Box 1, Item 2)
  - Distinguished Faculty Address. "Ravens and Polar Bear" James King. ITS. Tape Number PROV 2. Video: 3/4" U-matic. 60:12, undated (Box 1, Item 3)
  - Distinguished Faculty Address. "Mathematics and the Real World" Theodore Ostrom. ITS. Tape Number PROV 4. Video: 3/4" U-matic. 44:00, 1980 November 12 (Box 1, Item 4)
  - Distinguished Faculty Address (49th). "Adaptation: Challenges to and Responses of Skeletal Muscle" Philip D. Gollnick. Tape Number PROV 5. Video: 3/4" U-matic. 61:25, 1982 November 10 (Box 1, Item 5)
  - Distinguished Faculty Address. "Through a Looking Glass Wonderland Created by Chem. Students" Don Mateson. Tape Number Provost #7. Video: 3/4" U-matic. 58:20, 1984-10 (Box 1, Item 6)
  - 53rd Distinguished Faculty Address. Tape #1 Dr. James Cook - MASTER. Video: 3/4" U-matic. 60' tape, 1986 October 14 (Box 1, Item 7)
  - 53rd Distinguished Faculty Address. Tape #2 Dr. James Cook. Video: 3/4" U-matic. 60' tape, 1986 October 14 (Box 1, Item 8)
  - President's Convocation. Shirley Chisholm. Video: 3/4" U-matic. 60' tape, 1905 June 09 (Box 1, Item 9)
  - Faculty Development. Video: 3/4" U-matic. 60' tape, 1989 November 15 (Box 1, Item 10)
  - Faculty Development. Horne. Video: 3/4" U-matic. 60' tape, 1990 January 31 (Box 1, Item 11)
  - Faculty Development. Crane. Video: 3/4" U-matic. 60' tape, 1990 February 07 (Box 1, Item 12)
  - Faculty Development. Frederick. Video: 3/4" U-matic. 60' tape, 1990 March 26 (Box 1, Item 13)
  - Faculty Development. Banks. Video: 3/4" U-matic. 60' tape, 1990 April 03 (Box 1, Item 14)
  - Educational Forum on the Persian Gulf. Tape #1 Coliseum. Video: 3/4" U-matic. 60' tape, 1991 January 24 (Box 2, Item 1)
  - Educational Forum on the Persian Gulf. Tape #2 Coliseum. Video: 3/4" U-matic. 60' tape, 1991 January 24 (Box 2, Item 2)
  - "Gallagher 1991 - (Arlene Schnitzer Oct. 9) CH1: Comp and CH2:Comp Columbia Cable of Washington." Tape and case same label with DUPE noted and from Intersound Inc. of Los Angeles. Video: 3/4" U-matic. 10' tape?, 33487 (Box 2, Item 3)
  - Mini-University. Tape 1 Opening Titles Provost George. Video: 3/4" U-matic. 11:38, 1991 November 15 (Box 2, Item 4)
  - Mini-University. Tape 2 Dr. Tolmacheva. Video: 3/4" U-matic. 61:22, 1991 November 15 (Box 2, Item 5)
  - Mini-University. Tape 3 Dr. Wahl includes closing credits. Video: 3/4" U-matic. 36:00, 1991 November 15 (Box 2, Item 6)
  - WSU - John Kerwin. "Effective Television Communications with the Incarcerated" - labeled "edited master." 2 of 2. Video: 3/4" U-matic, 1993 (Box 2, Item 7)
  - Tape labeled RFK, Jr WSU Speech, Magrita Mendoza Ressler Smith 9-15-94, McSweeney 2-10-94, and Kennedy 11-13-96. Label on case notes only Kennedy. Video: 3/4" U-matic. 60'tape, 1994-1996 (Box 2, Item 8)
  - T. Kennedy "Hong Kong." Note identifies as Professor Tom Kennedy lecturing on Hong Kong about Chinese takeover. Video: 3/4" U-matic. 60' tape, 1997 February 12 (Box 2, Item 9)
  - Yevtushenko #1 - Yevgeny Yevtushenko reading - Bhatia lecture, University Honors Program. Program inside case. Tape says "Borlaug #2". Video: 3/4" U-matic. 30' tape?, 1997 March 08 (Box 2, Item 10)
  - Yevtushenko #2 - Yevgeny Yevtushenko reading - Bhatia lecture, University Honors Program. Video: 3/4" U-matic. 60' tape?, 1997 March 08 (Box 2, Item 11)
  - Bois-Joly #1 2-29-00. [May be about Space Shuttle disaster with Roger Boisjoly]. Video: 3/4" U-matic. 60' tape?, 2000 February 29 (Box 2, Item 12)
  - Bois-Joly #2 2-29-00. Video: 3/4" U-matic SP. 20' tape?, 2000 February 29 (Box 2, Item 13)
  - Bois-Joly #3 2-29-00 (on case spine and tape). Labeled on spine and post-it note on case reads: "details on space shuttle disaster by an engineer that worked on it". Video: 3/4" U-matic. 60' tape?, 2000 February 29 (Box 2, Item 14)
  - Sergei Khrushchev (son of former Russian premier). Video: 3/4" U-matic. 60' tape?, 2000 April 06 (Box 2, Item 15)
  - Asian/Pacific American Heritage Week: Redress Panel #1. Gordon Hirabayashi. Video: VHS, 1982 May 08 (Box 3, Item 1)
  - Asian/Pacific American Heritage Week: Redress Panel #2. Gordon Hirabayashi. Video: VHS, 1982 May 08 (Box 3, Item 2)
  - Bert Welliver Lecture. Video: VHS. 1:10:00, 1989 February 21 (Box 3, Item 3)
  - Pres. Convocation - Gov. Gardner. Video: VHS. 120' tape, 1989 October 20 (Box 3, Item 4)
  - Open Forum in CUB. Dr. Reginald Wilson, ACE. Video: VHS. 120' tape, 1990 December 04 (Box 3, Item 5)
  - Faculty Honors Convocation. Video: VHS, 2001 March 28 (Box 3, Item 6)
  - American Tragedy 9-14-01. Video: M II. 90' tape, 37148 (Box 3, Item 7)
  - Rights Panel 9-27-01 #1. Paper inside dated 12-17-04 notes that 8 tapes in MII format for 6 events were recordings of panel discussions regarding 9/11 attacks. Video: M II. 90' tape, 37161 (Box 3, Item 8)
  - Rights Panel #2 9-27-01 Panel #3 Panel #4. Video: M II. 90' tape, 37161 (Box 3, Item 9)
  - Middle East Panel #3. Video: M II. 90' tape, 2001 October 10 (Box 3, Item 10)
  - Panel #4 10-24-01 Anthrax. Video: M II. 90' tape, 2001 October 24 (Box 3, Item 11)
  - Panel #5 11-08-01. Video: M II. 90' tape, 2001 November 08 (Box 3, Item 12)
  - CUE Talk w/ Legislative Staff/Tour. Video: VHS, 2001 December 12 (Box 3, Item 13)
  - 9-11 Panel #1 9-19-02. Video: M II. 90' tape, 2001 September 19 (Box 3, Item 14)
  - 9-11 Panel #2 9-19-02. Video: M II. 90' tape, 2001 September 19 (Box 3, Item 15)
  - Tom Foley. Video: M II, 2003 March 11 (Box 3, Item 16)
  - Faculty Honors Convocation. Video: VHS. 60' tape, 2002 April 04 (Box 3, Item 17)
  - Faculty Honors Convocation. Raw Footage. Video: VHS. 120' tape, 2002 April 05 (Box 3, Item 18)
  - Weldon B. Gibson Distinguished Volunteer Award 2003. KWSU-TV. Video: VHS. 60' tape (Box 3, Item 19)
  - Donald Matteson. WSU Professor of Chemistry. Video: Betacam, undated (Box 3, Item 20)
  - Patrick Morgan Lecture at Kimbrough - Side A. Audio: 1/8" tape Standard Audio cassette. 60' tape, 1983 December 05 (Box 3, Item 21)
  - French Show - 1st Interview Pierre Solanger [sic] - John F. Kennedy's Press Secretary. Salinger - tape logo is KIRO Newsradio 71. Audio: 1/8" tape Standard Audio cassette, 1988 October 07 (Box 3, Item 22)
  - John Fabian Lecture MOF Side 1. Audio: 1/8" tape Standard Audio cassette. 45:00, 1995 March 11 (Box 3, Item 23)
  - WSU Spokane. Marilyn Baker speaking on HECB's Leadership Role in Changing Times. Audio: 1/8" tape Standard Audio cassette, undated (Box 3, Item 24)
  - Natural History of HIV - Medical Management. Dr. Gerberding; Dr. Sande. Audio: 1/8" tape Standard Audio cassette, undated (Box 3, Item 25)
  - "Academic Leadership for a Change Institutional Priorities for Change. Arthur Levine; Thomas F. George. Audio: 1/8" tape Standard Audio cassette", undated (Box 3, Item 26)
  - Henry Plummer on SALT II - Side A. Audio: 1/8" tape Standard Audio cassette. 90' tape, undated (Box 3, Item 27)
  - Burt Harrison Invited Address. Label on plastic case states "for Judith Leynse". Audio: 1/4" open reel audio tape. tape to outside of reel, 1975 March 19 (Box 3, Item 28)
  - First Distinguished Lecturer in Music History and Literature Hans Moldenhauer. "Arresting 20th Century Music History" Intro by Ruby Ronald to William Brandt's "Six Brevities" for piano. Inside box is program with notes on what is recorded on each tape. FR, 1987 March 01 (Box 3, Item 29)
  - First Distinguished Lecturer in Music History and Literature Hans Moldenhauer. "Arresting 20th Century Music History" Lecture by Moldenhauer. Intro by John F. Guido, Archives, WSU. FRT 3187-2. Audio: 1/4" open reel audio tape. 96' tape, 1987 March 01 (Box 3, Item 30)
  - Invited Address. Ruth Slonim. Audio: 1/4" open reel audio tape. 1200' tape, undated (Box 3, Item 31)
  - 21st Invited Address "Proems and Poems." Ruth Slonim - first woman to deliver WSU Distinguished Faculty Address. Audio: 1/4" open reel audio tape. 1200' tape, 1967 November 29 (Box 3, Item 32)
  - "For Ruth Slonim." Possibly copy of her address?. Audio: 1/4" open reel audio tape, undated (Box 3, Item 33)
  - Asian/Pacific American Heritage Week: Redress Panel. Gordon Hirabayashi. Digital Video: DVD, 1982 May 08 (Box 3, Item 34)
  - Weldon B. Gibson Distinguished Volunteer Award 2005. KWSU and KTNW. Digital Video: DVD-R (Box 3, Item 35)
  - WSU Global Oil Depletion and Implications for the Pacific Northwest. Rep. Cathy McMorris and Senator Patty Murray, Spokane. Digital Video: DVD-R, 2005 October 04/2005 October 05 (Box 3, Item 36)
- SERIES 2: RECRUITMENT AND PROMOTIONAL MEDIA.
  - "Now and for the Future" spots. Video: 3/4" U-matic, 1983 March 01 (Box 4, Item 1)
  - WSU Recruitment Video (Relations Dept). Glenn Johnson narrator. Master. Video: 3/4" U-matic. TRT 4:58, 1980s late (Box 4, Item 2)
  - WSU Spokane. Continuing Education. Video: 3/4" U-matic, 1988 (Box 4, Item 3)
  - Centennial PSAs: Murrow (:30), Great University (:15), What's Different? (:30). Video: 3/4" U-matic, 1989-07 (Box 4, Item 4)
  - WSU PSAs(2): What's the Difference; Murrow. Video: 3/4" U-matic, 1991 (Box 4, Item 5)
  - Washington State University #1 and 2. Video: 3/4" U-matic, 1992-02 (Box 4, Item 6)
  - The Road to Education. Video: 3/4" U-matic. 11:58, 33911 (Box 4, Item 7)
  - WSU Recruitment Tape. Video: 3/4" U-matic. 5:00, undated (Box 4, Item 8)
  - 7 clips, 6 are 30" and one called "Pullman Parent" is 10" others are "Pullman Parent," "Pullman Student" and ones for each of branch campus (Spokane, Tri-Cities, and Vancouver) as well as "WSU EDP Program." Video: 1" Open reel video tape Type C. 3:10, 1997-06 (Box 4, Item 9)
  - WSU New Horizons. Video: 3/4" U-matic (small). TRT 11:30, undated (Box 4, Item 10)
  - A Matter of Choice. 12 min. Financial Aid at WSU. 14 min. Video: VHS. 26 min., 1988 (Box 4, Item 11)
  - WSU Spots: :30 Murrow, :15 Great University, :30 What's Different, :30 Teaching. RXL Productions (Spokane). Video: VHS, 1991-11 (Box 4, Item 12)
  - Campaign WSU. Video: VHS. 13:30, 1992 October 23 (Box 5, Item 1)
  - Campaign WSU PSAs: Valerie Garza, Jesse Harris, Leroy Ashby, Akuzi Beans, Taxol. All five are 30 seconds. Video: Betacam, undated (Box 5, Item 2)
  - WSU Parent 1x:10. Video: VHS, 1997 March 31 (Box 5, Item 3)
  - WSU Recruitment Video - WSU Alumni Association. Video: VHS. TRT 9:02, 1998 (Box 5, Item 4)
  - WSU Campus Video. Video: VHS. 9 min., 1998 (Box 5, Item 5)
  - Recruitment video. Video: VHS, 2000-Fall (Box 5, Item 6)
  - WSU Recruitment Video 2001. Video: VHS. 8 min. (Box 5, Item 7)
  - "World Class. Face to Face." Campaign. TV Spots: Engineering, French, Student Recreation Center. 30 sec. each, 2001-08 (Box 5, Item 8)
  - "World Class. Face to Face." Campaign. PSA's: Be a Teacher, Good Grades, Research. Video: VHS. 30 sec. each, 2001-09 (Box 5, Item 9)
  - WSU Recruitment Video 2002. Video: VHS. 9 min. (Box 5, Item 10)
  - Student Recruitment Campaign Public Service Announcements. Video: VHS. 30 sec. ea. (10 min. tape), 2002-10 (Box 5, Item 11)
  - New Horizons Slideshow. Alumni Office. Video: VHS, undated (Box 6, Item 1)
  - Discarded 6-10-2015. MOE. (Box 6, Item 2)
  - Washington State University Showcasing Academic Excellence. Video: VHS. ~10 min, undated (Box 6, Item 3)
  - WSU Draft Recruiting Video. Video: VHS, undated (Box 6, Item 4)
  - WSU Example. Video: VHS, undated (Box 6, Item 5)
  - WSU Promotional Spots. Transmitted via WHETS with some quality lost. Video: VHS, undated (Box 6, Item 6)
  - WSU PSAs. Video: VHS, undated (Box 6, Item 7)
  - WSU PSAs (general). Video: VHS, undated (Box 6, Item 8)
  - WSU Recruitment Video (Long Version). Video: VHS. A few minutes, undated (Box 6, Item 9)
  - WSU Spots. 4 PSAs: 3 centennial; 1 professors. Video: VHS, undated (Box 6, Item 10)
  - WSU Television Spot. Video: VHS. A few minutes, undated (Box 6, Item 11)
  - WSU Biotech. Video: VHS, undated (Box 7, Item 1)
  - WSU College of Business and Economics. Video: VHS. 7:00, undated (Box 7, Item 2)
  - WSU/UW "Pharmacy in Washington State." Video: VHS., 2002 January 17 (Box 7, Item 3)
  - News article about "Pharmacy in Washington State." Paper., undated (Box 7, Item 0)
  - WSU Recruiting and Retaining Students of Color. Video: VHS, undated (Box 7, Item 4)
  - WSU Hispanic Recruitment Video. Aaron Haskins on post-it note attached. Video: VHS. 10:45, undated (Box 7, Item 5)
  - Washington State University International. Video: VHS, 2000 (Box 7, Item 6)
  - Extended Degree Program "Road to Education." Video: VHS. 11:58, 1993 (Box 7, Item 7)
  - WSU Extended Degree Commercial. Video: VHS, 1995-04 (Box 7, Item 8)
  - WSU At A Distance. Video: VHS. TRT 5:30, 1998-10 (Box 7, Item 9)
  - EDP Sample Reel. Extended Degree Programs. Video: VHS. 20 min., 2000 (Box 7, Item 10)
  - EDP "Getting Here from There." Extended Degree Programs. Video: VHS, 2000 (Box 7, Item 11)
  - EDP Spot 1X 30 (NO TAG). Video: VHS. 120' tape, undated (Box 8, Item 1)
  - Washington Higher Education Telecommunication System promo, produced by Don Peters. Radio-Television Services. Video: VHS. 5 min., undated (Box 8, Item 2)
  - WSU: 1) WSU "EDP-Program" 2) WSU "Spokane" 3) WSU "Tri-Cities" 4) WSU "Vancouver" 5) Pullman Parent 6) Pullman Student. 6x:30. Video: VHS, 1998 May 26 (Box 8, Item 3)
  - WSU Spokane. Nancy Hilliard. Video: VHS. 0:30, undated (Box 8, Item 4)
  - WSU Tri-Cities "Opening Doors to your Future." Video: VHS. 6:20, undated (Box 8, Item 5)
  - WSU Tri-Cities 30 sec. Commercial. Video: VHS. 00:30, 1996-07 (Box 8, Item 6)
  - WSU Vancouver 1x:30. Video: VHS. 30 sec., 1997 March 05 (Box 8, Item 7)
  - WSU Vancouver TV Spot :30 Summer '98 copy 2/2. Video: VHS. 120' tape, 1998 (Box 8, Item 8)
  - A Great Place to Grow: Moscow, Idaho, Pullman, Washington. Video: VHS, 1999 (Box 8, Item 9)
  - WSU Spokane. Audio: 1/8" tape Standard Audio cassette. 00:00:30, undated (Box 8, Item 10)
  - WSU Spokane. Audio: 1/8" tape Standard Audio cassette. 00:00:30, 19uu July 30 (Box 8, Item 11)
  - WSU: World Class. Face to Face. General student recruitment (Possibly introduction of World Class Face to Face tagline?). Digital Video: CD. 46 mb, 2001 (Box 8, Item 12)
  - WSU: International. Digital Video: CD. 491 mb, 2000 (Box 8, Item 13)
  - WSU: International. Digital Video: CD. 243 mb, 2004 (Box 8, Item 14)
  - 8-track tape no label and missing black rubber pinch roller. KUGR. Audio: 8-track audio tape. :70, undated (Box 8, Item 15)
  - Metal case labeled "This is W.S.C." WSU Audio Visual Center label on metal case. Film: 16mm - w. audio, color. ~1000 feet, 1952 (Box 9, Item 1)
  - This is W.S.C. (Master) on case with 22 min and 1953 (handwritten date) on label from Instructional Media Services at WSU. Video: VHS. 22 or 26 min., 1952 (Box 9, Item 2)
  - This is WSC. Video: VHS, 1952 (Box 9, Item 3)
  - This Is W.S.C. Edward R. Murrow. VHS 18859. Video: VHS, 1952 (Box 9, Item 4)
  - This is W.S.U. (Master) on case with 26 min and 1963 (handwritten date) on label from Instructional Media Services at WSU. Video: VHS, 1962 (Box 9, Item 5)
  - WSU's 90th Anniversary. Video: 3/4" U-matic. 30 min., 1980-04 (Box 9, Item 6)
  - "Old Wazzu" (Cougar Spirit) Film Presentation #1. Case has checkout card on it and film reel labeled L.R.C. Film: 16mm - w. audio, color, 1981 (Box 9, Item 7)
  - Old Wazzu "#4." Film: Super 16mm. 400'; ~13 min., 1981 (Box 9, Item 8)
  - "WSU Spirit" on case but this is Old Wazzu. Film: Super 16mm. 400'; ~13 min., 1981 (Box 9, Item 9)
  - Cougar Athletics: Do You Remember (may be "Old Wazzu"). Video: VHS, 1981 (Box 9, Item 10)
  - "Old Wasu." Produced by Vik-Winkle. Video: 3/4" U-matic, 1981 (Box 9, Item 11)
  - Centennial program. Video: 3/4" U-matic. 29:40, circa 1990 (Box 9, Item 12)